Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series VI. Printed materials, 1922-1946; 11 boxes, 5.5 lin. feet
  A few miscellaneous printed items. No detailed inventory currently available.